(Arthur:)Sheldon, what are you doing here?
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry. Did I wake you?
(Arthur:)Of course you woke me.
It's 7:30.
(Sheldon:)Well, I would have been here sooner,
but for some reason your home
(Sheldon:)isn't on this map of Hollywood stars.
(Arthur:)What do you want, Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)It's been pointed out
by my girlfriend
(Sheldon:)that I may have been annoying to you.
(Arthur:)She sounds like a keeper.
(Sheldon:)Anyway, I wanted to apologize.
I am truly sorry.
(Arthur:)All right, apology accepted.
Have a nice night.
(Sheldon:)Now that we've cleared the air,
(Sheldon:)I wanted to discuss
another matter with you.
(Arthur:)Sheldon, in a couple hours,
I have to get up,
(Arthur:)pee and then wander
around the house.
(Sheldon:)Well, then, I'll make this quick.
(Sheldon:)I want to talk about the paper
you sent Leonard.